nextonemedia.com 2018-10-02

# Nextone Media - Corporate

Internet privacy is an issue that Nextone Media takes very seriously. Each of our Web sites has a posted privacy policy so that you, as a user of the site, can understand what information is being collected about you and how that information is being used. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that Nextone Media Limited collects, and the ways in which Nextone Media Limited uses that personal information.

Under the Data Protection Act 1998, we have a legal duty to protect any information we collect from you. We use leading technologies and encryption software to safeguard your data, and keep strict security standards to prevent any unauthorised access to it.  
We do not pass on your details to any third party or government department unless you give us permission to do so.

## Personal information collection

Nextone Media Limited may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * [information about your use of this website (including all our brand Web sites);]
  * [information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website (including all our brand Web sites);]
  * [information about transactions carried out over this website (including all our brand Web sites);] 
  * [information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services (including all our brand Web sites); and]
  * [any other information that you send to Nextone Media Limited.]

## Using personal information

Nextone Media Limited may use your personal information to:

  * [administer this website;]
  * [personalize the website for you;]
  * [enable your access to and use of the website services;]
  * [publish information about you on the website;]
  * [send to you products that you purchase;]
  * [supply to you services that you purchase;]
  * [send you statements and invoices;]
  * [collect payments from you; and]
  * [send you marketing communications.]

Where Nextone Media Limited discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, Nextone Media Limited may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

## Securing your data

Nextone Media Limited will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

Nextone Media Limited will store all the personal information you provide on its secure servers.

## Cross-border data transfers

Information that Nextone Media Limited collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which Nextone Media Limited operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

## Cookies

A cookie consists of information sent by a web server to a web browser, and stored by the browser. The information is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. This enables the web server to identify and track the web browser.

We may use both “session” cookies [and “persistent” cookies on the website. We will use the session cookies to: keep track of you whilst you navigate the website. We will use the persistent cookies to: enable our website to recognise you when you visit.

Session cookies will be deleted from your computer when you close your browser. Persistent cookies will remain stored on your computer until deleted, or until they reach a specified expiry date.

We use Google Analytics to analyse the use of our websites. Google Analytics generates statistical and other information about website use by means of cookies, which are stored on users' computers. The information generated relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of the website. Google will store this information. Google's privacy policy is available at: http://www.google.com/privacypolicy.html.

Our advertisers/payment services providers may also send you cookies.

We publish Google Adsense interest-based advertisements on our website. These are tailored by Google to reflect your interests. To determine your interests, Google will track your behaviour across the web using cookies. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser using Google's Ads Preference Manager, available at: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/. You can opt-out of the Adsense partner network cookie at: http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html. However, this opt-out mechanism uses a cookie, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained. To ensure that an opt-out is maintained in respect of a particular browser, you should use the Google browser plug-in available at: http://www.google.com/ads/preferences/plugin

Most browsers allow you to reject all cookies, whilst some browsers allow you to reject just third party cookies. For example, in Internet Explorer you can refuse all cookies by clicking “Tools”, “Internet Options”, “Privacy”, and selecting “Block all cookies” using the sliding selector. Blocking all cookies will, however, have a negative impact upon the usability of many websites, including this one.

## Updating this statement

Nextone Media Limited may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

## Other websites

This website contains links to other websites.

Nextone Media Limited is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

## Contact Nextone Media Limited

If you have any questions about this privacy policy or Nextone’s treatment of your personal information, please write to:

Nextone Media Limited  
147 Station Road  
North Chingford, London  
E4 6AG, United Kingdom.
